May I ask your name?
お名前聞いてもいいですか?
This is Saya.
さやです
Saya-chan.
さやちゃん
You're young.
若いね
Are you wearing shoes? How old are you?
おりくつですか、お年は?
Did you just graduate?
卒業したばっかり?
Are you a first year university student?
大学1年生ってこと?
yes.
はい
That's nice.
いいですね
Do you know what we're filming today?
今日は何の撮影か知ってます?
Well, yes.
まあ、はい
Do you know?
知ってる?
Yeah.
うん
Naughty photo shoot?
エッチな撮影?
yes.
はい
Do you like sex?
エッチのことは好きですか?
By the way, can I ask how many people have experience?
ちなみに、経験人数を聞いてもいいですか?
About 50.
50くらい
50?
Seriously?
マジ?
Amazing, at 18 years old.
すごいね、18歳で
What do you mean, classmate?
それはどういう、同級生ってこと?
Some kind of app.
なんかアプリで
App?
アプリ?
Eh.
えー
So, did you find many people older than you?
じゃあ、自分が年上の相手が多かったんですか?
Do you invite it yourself?
それは自分から誘う?
Well, us too.
まあ、うちも
I said let's meet on the app,
アプリで会おうよって言ってあって、
What should I do first?
最初どうすんの?
No, it's time to do it.
いや、もうやろうっていう手ですから
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなの
So, is it like going straight to Potel?
じゃあ、ポテル直行みたいなの?
Almost.
ほぼ
Seriously?
マジか
I really like sex.
めちゃくちゃ好きなエッチ
Yeah.
うん
That's great.
それは素晴らしいね
The eldest was like, well, was that a good thing?
一番年上は、じゃあ、そんなのよかったのか?
Good thing.
いいこと
I felt like that was the max.
それぐらいがマックスって感じだった
Is this okay if you are older?
これは全然、年上だったら大丈夫ですか?
The first.
初の
Is there a sexual experience that excites you the most?
一番興奮したエッチとか、あるんですか?
Well, there are various things about foreigners...
なんか、外国人って、まあ、いろいろ...
I agree.
そうだね
Size etc.
サイズとか
技術
Did technology do that?
技術がそうやった?
Seriously?
マジか
The Japanese still can't win.
中々、日本人はまだ勝てない
So, do you like it big?
じゃあ、大きいのが好きですか?
When was the first time you had sex?
初めてエッチしたのはいつ?
It's May 1st.
5月1日です
Is it an app then too?
その時もアプリ?
No, maybe yes.
いや、たぶん、はい
Ah, the first recent app?
あ、初最近アプリ?
Eh, why did you want to have sex like that?
えー、なんでそんなエッチしたかったの?
No, not like Simon.
いや、サイモン的ではなく
Ah, just like looking for friends.
ああ、普通に友達探しみたいな
So, did you feel like you discovered the goodness of sex there?
じゃあ、そこでエッチの良さに目覚めた感じですか?
By the way, is Saya-chan S or M?
ちなみに、さやちゃんはSかMかというと、
Which one?
どっち?
It's M.
Mです
Pretty M.
結構とM
It was like being strangled.
結 構、首締められたりね
I was stuffed with words.
言葉詰めされたり
Even though it's so cute.
そんなに可愛いのにね
On the other hand, don't you have classmates?
逆に同級生とかないの?
No.
ないです
No, Zero.
ないんだ、ゼロ
Let's go, you two.
行こうよ、2人
Let's go.
行こうよ
Is that the same school?
それ、同じ学校?
Is that all?
それだけ?
Didn't you find out at school?
学校ではバレなかったの?
Is that so?
そんなの?
Maybe it's okay.
た ぶん、大丈夫です
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
What kind of character were you at school?
学校ではどんなキャラだったんですか?
fine.
元気
Ah, I'm fine.
あ、元気
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Did you do it in the past?
昔とかやってた?
yes.
はい
What do you do?
何をですか?
Ah, this is impossible.
あ、これは無理です
Impossible?
無理?
Can't you say that?
それは言えないの?
運動系?
Not.
じゃない
Isn't it cultural?
じゃない、文化系?
It seems like it's really popular though.
めちゃめちゃモテそうだけどね
No, I don't want to be popular.
いや、モテたくない
Seriously?
マジで?
You want to be confessed to, right?
告白されたいでしょ?
Isn't that your word?
それはお言葉でしょ?
不同級生?
do not have.
ない
By the way, how many centimeters are you tall?
ちなみに、身長とかは何センチなんですか?
158, good.
158、いい
Do you get picked up a lot?
結構、ナンパとかされるんですか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Not at all.
全然ない
By the way, where is your university?
ちなみに、大学はどこですか?
It's Meiji.
明治です
Meiji.
明治
Can I put away the student awards?
学生賞もしまっていいですか?
The student award is also cute
学生賞もかわいい
hey.
ね
Well then, you're popular.
じゃあ、 モテそう
Have you been confessed to by your seniors at university?
大学で先輩とかに告白されてます?
no.
いや
think?
考える?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
That's fine.
いいです
Is that okay?
そういうのはいいの?
yes.
はい
So, will you continue using the app?
じゃあ、これからもアプリ続けるんですか?
yes.
はい
Is it different from someone you don't know?
知らない人とは違う?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
No, that's not it.
いや、そういうことでもなく
I want someone who is used to it.
慣れてる人がいい
Ah, I like good people.
あ、うまい人がいい
I see.
なるほど
Shall we take it off?
脱いでってみましょうか
It's really tight.
めっちゃ引き締まってるね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Aren't your abdominal muscles cracked?
腹筋割れてない?
No, it's not broken.
いや、割れてない
amazing.
すごい
I don't play any sports.
なんもスポーツやってない
do not have.
ない
That's amazing.
すごいね
natural.
天然
With sex.
セックスで
Yeah.
うん
It was sex.
セックスでしまった
By the way, when was the last time you did it?
ちなみに直近だといつしたんですか?
The day before yesterday.
おととい
Who was your opponent yesterday?
おととい、相手は?
The other person is...
相手は...
First time person?
初めての人?
No, several times.
いや、何回か
Regular?
定期?
Regular.
定期
Regular sex friend?
定期セフレ?
Are people like that wasteful?
そういう人はごむしてあるの?
No, I haven't.
いや、してない
I haven't.
してない
Nothing?
なんも?
Well, to people...
まあ、人に...
That's life.
その人生なんだ
Who is OK with that life?
その人生でOKな人?
Is that person the main character?
その人が結構メインだったりするの?
Main sex friend?
メインセフレ?
No, it's not.
いや、違います
different?
違う?
What else is the main thing?
メインは他に?
No, it's not.
いや、違います
Didn't that person say anything about going out with you?
別にその人は一つ付き合おうとは言ってないの?
No.
ならない
Then no.
なら ない
By the way, how many cups is this?
ちなみにこれ何カップなんですか?
I think it's C.
Cだと思います
C cup?
Cカップ?
cute.
かわいい
Maybe it's a bit of perspective.
ちょっと目線だいかもしれない
Until Maeda.
前田まで
It might have been a high school student.
高校生だったかも
Congratulations on your graduation.
卒業おめでとうございます
Shall I try removing the plastic jacket?
プラジャン外してみようか
You're used to it.
手慣れてるね
Aren't you embarrassed?
恥ずかしくない?
yes.
はい
Are you used to being taken?
もう取られ慣れてんの?
no.
いや
Move your hands behind your head.
手を頭の後ろに変えて
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Do you know this?
これ知ってる?
What do you see often?
よく見るやつ?
Not good.
よくはない
Don't you look closely?
よく見ないの?
it hurts.
痛い
I'm really used to it.
すっごい慣れてるね
Well then, let's try those pants.
じゃあそのパンツにでみようか
Put your hands behind your back.
手を後ろにして
Yeah?
うん?
How do you feel?
どんな気持ちですか?
Shall we make an M-shape?
M字になってみようか
Open your pussy.
おまんこ開いてみて
So stick your butt out.
で、お尻突き出してね
Then try opening your butt with both hands.
じゃあ両手でお尻開いてみて
I can see it completely.
めっちゃ丸見えるよ
Should I ask Daiyu-san to tell me?
大優さんに言ってもらおうか
It's Uncle and Oesu.
おじさんとオエスなんだよね
I get embarrassed when people stare at me.
見つめられちゃうと照れちゃう
Could you give me a bell?
ベル出してもらえた?
It's true, Bell.
本当だよ、ベル
That's a good answer.
いい答えだね
I'm glad it's finished.
仕上がっていいよね
It's new.
新しいね
It's big.
大きいですよ
TRUE?
本当?
cute.
かわいい
It's super cute.
超かわいいね
Do you like yourself?
自分好きなの?
You said it earlier.
さっき言ってたよね
Do you like yourself today?
今日自分好きなの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Until now by myself
今まで自分で
difference.
さ
I don't know if I put too many in there.
い っぱい入れすぎてわかんないの
TRUE?
本当?
That's amazing.
すごいな
What can you do?
なんでられますか?
That's cool.
かっこいいな
I'll see your face.
顔見ちゃうよ
By myself.
自分でさ
Would you like me to put my foot up?
足掲げてもらおうか
So that you can see well.
よく見えるように
Show me right away.
早速見せて
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Are you moving comfortably?
気持ちよく動いてるの?
Yeah.
うん
It's sparkling.
きらめちゃ
Hmm.
うーん
う ーん
Hmm.
うーん
う ーん
Hmm.
うーん
You don't have to rum.
ラムをしないでいいから
Ask your doctor.
お医者に聞かせてよ
To a child who feels good.
気持ちいい子へ
Hmm.
うーん
う ーん
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃないの?
Please lick me more.
もっと舐めてください
Please lick it more.
も っと舐めてください
Do you want me to lick you more?
もっと舐めてほしい?
Yeah.
うん
real?
ほんと?
Well then, I'll lick it instead.
じゃあいいんじゃなく舐めるよ
Yeah.
うん
It's true.
ほんとだね
Drool once.
ヨダレ一回つけ
All you have to do is drool once.
ヨダレ一回つければな
Looks like I can eat it.
チンチン食えるみたい
Do it.
やらして
I get excited just looking at it.
見てるだけ興奮しちゃう
Look for drool.
ヨダレ探して
He's a bad boy.
悪い子だなぁ
it's okay.
いいんだよ
Don't do it too much.
あんましないで
I want to hear it.
聞きたいんだ
Ichi's voice.
イチの声
Hey.
ねえ
Yeah.
うん
I cry even more.
も っと泣くんだよ
Look.
ほら
When you feel good, you don't have to do so much.
気持ちいいとき、 あんましなくていいんだよ
After all, you have such a cute face.
せっかくこんな可愛い顔してんだからさ
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
Don't even call me.
電話もしないで
If you want to listen, you can just go there.
聞きたいときは、 行 っちゃっていいんだからね
Look.
ほら
Look, if I won, I would cry.
ほら、当たったら 泣くのってきちゃったね
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
I'm a shy person.
恥ずかしがり屋さんなんだ
Yeah.
うん
I need to free myself more.
もっと自分解放しちゃいなよ
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
Yeah.
うん
If there's nothing good about it, I'll stop.
いいとこないならやめちゃうよ
After all, it doesn't feel good.
だって気持ちいいじゃないんだもん
I have to speak out.
声出さないと
Yeah.
うん
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
Feels good.
いい感じ
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
cry.
泣く
Cry.
泣 く
I'm not quitting yet.
まだやめないよ
Not yet, not yet.
まだ、まだ
Yeah.
うん
Not yet.
まだだよ
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
I'll keep going.
続けて行っちゃうよ
Yeah.
うん
go?
行く?
Will you go again?
また行く?
Are you going again?
また行くのか
He's a naughty kid.
やらしい子だね
Look.
ほら
I'm going.
行っちゃうよ
Look.
ほ ら
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
It's still not enough.
まだ足りないだろ
Yeah.
うん
If I have to stop, I will.
やめるならやめるよ
Yeah.
うん
If you don't like it, tell me you don't like it.
嫌なら嫌だって教えて
Isn't there?
ないの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you want to go further?
もっと行きたいの?
Please do more.
もっとやってくださいって
Yeah.
うん
Please do more.
もっとやってくださいって
Please do me a favor.
ちゃんとお願いしろ
Please do more.
もっとやってくださいって
Okay, okay.
よしよしよし
He's a good boy, he's a good boy.
いい子だ、いい子だ
Yeah.
うん
Show me your naughty face.
やらしい顔見せろ
Look.
ほ ら
Yeah.
うん
Look.
ほら
It was making a lot of noise.
めっちゃ音してきたね
yes.
はい
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
go?
行く?
行 く?
Wow.
うわっ
It was hollowed out.
くり開いちゃった
copper?
どう?
I could see her ass hole completely.
お尻の穴まで丸見えたよ
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever had your butthole played with?
お尻の穴っていじられたことあんの?
Yeah.
うん
うんなんだ
Do you like having your butthole licked too?
お尻の穴も舐められても好き?
Don't you like it?
好きじゃないの?
Don't do it?
やっちゃダメ?
No.
ダメ
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
What?
なんて?
Because it's embarrassing?
恥ずかしいから?
Okay, fine.
よし、いいよ
This is where I put it.
掲げとこだ
Come on, come on.
さあさあ
Okay.
よし
Let's go.
行くぞ
Look at this.
見てごらん、こっち
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
Yeah.
うん
I was licked by your uncle,
あんのおじさんにのばんこ舐められてんだよ、
Look.
ほら
That's how I feel, you know.
あんな気分だ、ほら
Yeah?
うん?
Yeah.
うん
There's a nasty smell everywhere.
どこにだってやらしい匂いしてきてるぞ、
Look.
ほら
Yeah.
うん
Look at your face, come on.
顔見てね、ほら
Yeah.
うん
You look at me, here.
あんたこっち見るんだよ、ほら
Look here.
こっち見ろ
Yeah?
うん?
Look closely, here you go.
よく見ろ、ほらほら
It's your face.
あんた顔だ
Hmm.
んー
ん ー
Wow, you were there, look.
うわ、あんたいたよ、ほら
Hmm.
んー
ん ー
Hmm.
んー
You're amazing.
あんたすごい
Hey there.
ほ らほら
Look, you're being serious here.
ほら、マジでいいんだろ、ここ
Look, I just said that.
ほら、さっき言ったばっかりだもんな
I'm still going, you know.
まだ行っちゃうだろ、ほら
It's sensitive.
敏感だって
Look, look, look.
ほら、ほら、ほら
Look, don't hold back, look.
ほ ら、我慢すんな、ほら
Go, look.
行け、ほら
Hey, hey.
ちょっと、こ
I wonder what kind of penis your uncle has.
おじさんのおちんち、どんなおちんちだろうね
fun?
楽しみ?
Yeah.
うん
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
You can take a look.
見ていいよ
copper?
どう?
Look carefully.
よく見て
copper?
どう?
Good.
良き
happy?
嬉しい?
Taste it well.
よく味わって
Yeah.
うん
Ah, it's it.
あー、イッチだね
You know how to make a man happy, right?
どうやったら男の人が喜ぶか知ってるんだよね、
I'm sure.
きっとね
I guess this kind of thing feels good to me.
自分がさ、こういうの気持ちいいんだろうな
If you think it will make people happy, do it all.
喜んでもらえるんだろうな、と思う人は全部やってこな
Let's tie your hair in the back.
髪の毛結んじゃおうか、後ろで
Yeah.
うん
That's cute too.
それ もかわいいね
She has a cute face, so it's better not to hide her hair.
かわいい顔だから、髪の毛隠れないほうがいいよ
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
ah,
あー、
It's so cute.
ち っかかわいいんだからさ
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
Ah, it goes all the way in.
あー、奥まで入るね
Just use your mouth and slowly take it all the way in.
口だけで、ゆっくり奥まで入れとくな
Enter more, enter more.
もっと入る、もっと入る
See, that's right.
ほら、そうだよ
That's right, that's right.
そうだ、そうだ
Ah, that's painful.
あー、苦しいね
But you like it, don't you?
でも、好きだろ
The back of your throat.
喉の奥
I like it, don't I?
好きだよね
I understand, uncle.
分かるんだよ、おじさん
Because it's DOES.
ドエスだから
Look.
ほら
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
Ah, amazing.
あー、すごい
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうだよ
sad.
悲しい
You came out for a lot of hands.
いっぱい手のために出たね
That's good.
それがいいんだよ
Go all the way by yourself.
自分で奥まで
This time, I won't be able to hold your head, so I won't let you come all the way out on your own.
今度は頭を押さえられないで、自分で奥まで出とくな
He's a capable kid.
できる子だ
Try taking it out and putting it in slowly.
ゆっくり奥まで出したり、入れたりしてごらん
that.
それ
As much as I can get it myself.
自分で得づくぐらい
Shiko?
しーこ?
Do you hate pain?
苦しいの嫌?
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃないの?
It's M.
Mだもんな
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうだ
That's right.
そうだ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
My face is getting younger and younger.
どんどん顔が若くなってきた
It's painful.
苦しいんだ
You like pain, right?
苦しいの好きだろ
Hey.
なあ
Look.
ほら
ほ ら
Look.
ほら
That's right.
そうだよ
He's good at it.
上手だ
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
Oh, yes, drool.
あー、そうよだれ
I wanted that drool.
そのよだれが欲しかったんだ
Try licking the head too.
頭の方も舐めてごらん
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうだ
Do you see me as a good girl?
いい子って見るのかな?
Try putting the head and the rod tightly in your mouth.
頭を、竿を口の中にギュッて含んでごらん
You can inhale it.
吸い込んでいいから
Ah, yes.
あー、そう
The drooling penis was shiny and shiny.
よだれのおちんちんがピカピカに光った
Look, uncle's rod.
ほら、おじさんの竿
Is it delicious?
美味しいか?
Yeah.
うん
Which do you prefer, the rod or the rod?
竿と竿と、どっちが好き?
Both.
どっちも
Do you like both?
どっちも好きなの?
It's crazy.
くばりだね
Let's lick the dick.
ちんちん舐めてみよう
Hey, look at the camera.
ほら、カメラ見て
It's a waste because it's so cute.
せっかく可愛いんだから、もったいないよ
If I had said the following.
下も言ってたら
Hey.
ね え
I'm so impressed with this cute face.
感動がつかないよ、この可愛い顔
I need you to show me properly.
ちゃんと見せてくれないとさ
Put it all the way in yourself.
自分で、奥まで入れて
Please stop at the back.
奥で止めてごらん
Gyu.
ギューって
Water bear, look at me.
水くまで、こっち見て
On top of the waves.
波の上になって
Look above the waves.
波の上見ててよ
No, Dashi-chan.
ダメだよ、だしちゃん
That's no good, Dashi-chan.
ダメでしょ、だしちゃん
To the back.
奥まで
It's all the way in, look at me.
奥まで入れんだよ、こっち見て
Hey, stop it.
ほ ら、止めろ
Stop inside.
奥で止めろ
Deeper, deeper.
奥で、もっと奥
It's okay, go deeper.
いいんだろ、もっと奥
If I don't like it, I'll stop.
嫌ならやめちゃうよ
Yes, you can.
そう、できるのに
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
It's amazing, I'm drooling all over it.
すごいね、よだれいっぱいで
Hey, this way.
おい で、こっち
Lots of drool.
よ だれいっぱい
Give me some drool.
よだれちょうだい
It's cute how she nods when someone calls her cute.
可愛いって言われて、うんって頷くところが可愛い
Really cute.
本当に可愛い
It's tight.
ギュッとしてる
Ah, it tastes like my uncle's dick.
あー、おじさんのおチンチンの味がする
What do you want to do?
どうしたいんだ?
There is.
いる
Where?
どこに?
Here.
ここに
I don't know here.
ここじゃわかんないよ
what?
何?
You haven't said anything.
何も言ってないじゃん
What are you doing?
何かってなことしてるの?
You have to ask, right?
お願いしなきゃダメでしょ?
please.
お願いします
You're just trying to make yourself feel good.
自分ばっかり気持ちよくなおうとしてるだろ
Make yourself comfortable, come on.
気持ちよくしろよ、ほら
Come a little earlier and put it in front of you.
ちょっと前に来て、手前に置いて
Yes, that's it.
そうだ、それだ
You sounded good.
いい声出してきたね
It's making a weird sound.
やわしい音してるね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいのか?
tell me.
教えて
Tell me in words.
言葉にして教えて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
Does it feel good yet?
もう気持ちいいか
Hey, move!
ほら、動けほら
That's right.
そうだ
It's kind of closed.
なんか閉まってるぞ
Neck: It closes when you close it.
首 閉めると閉まるんだ
My face is getting redder and redder.
どんどん顔赤くなってきてる
My nose is also running.
鼻水も出てきてる
cute.
かわいい
So cute.
すんごいかわいい
My face is turning bright red.
真っ赤になってきたよ、顔が
Is it painful?
苦しいか?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいか?
Which one?
どっちだ?
Both?
両方か?
Look, look, look.
ほら、ほら、ほら、ほら
Why is there a sound this time, the sound of a scable?
なんで今度は音、スケーブルの音出しやがって
Look, look, look.
ほら、ほら、ほら
It's somewhere.
どこかだってる
Is it somewhere?
どこかだってるか
Oh my gosh, I can see how you really feel.
やばい、本気で感じてくれてるのわかるよ
Good luck.
うまくいけ
Look, Chris, you're rubbing off on me.
ほら、クリスちゃんこすれてるでしょ
Let's go, come on.
行っちゃえよ、ほら
行 っちゃえよ、ほら
Igui, Igui.
いぐい、いぐい
Ah, I was a little concerned.
あ、少し、気だった
Do you want it?
ほしい?
Yes, I want it.
うん、ほしい
I'll type it in.
打ち込むぞ
Ah, amazing.
あ〜、すごい
I'm having a lot of fun.
よくちゃぶれてる
Look, look, it's a big mess.
ほら、ほら、大まんくしまってる
Ho
ほ
Hey, what are you doing?
ら、 ほら、何してんだよ
Close your legs, close your legs, close your legs.
足閉じろ、足閉じろ、足閉じて
That's right, keep pushing.
そうそう、押し付き出したままで
I did that, I did that, I did that, I did that.
そうした、そうした、そうした、そうした
Look, there's something white coming out of my pussy.
ほら、なんかまんこから白いもの出てるぞ
Lend me your hand.
手貸して
both.
両方
Okay.
よ い しょ
What do you think?
どうだ
Look,
ほら、
Oi: Because it's stored away.
大 まんくしまってるから
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいのか?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm begging you to do more.
もっとしてくださいってお願いしてる
Yo
よ
It's ruined.
く ちゃぶれてる
Look, look, it's a big mess.
ほら、ほら、大まんくしまってる
Hey, what are you doing?
ほら、何してんだよ
Close your legs, close your legs, close your legs.
足閉じろ、足閉じろ、足閉じて
That's right, keep pushing.
そうそう、押し付き出したままで
Lend me your hand.
手貸して
both.
両 方
Good.
よいしょ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいのか?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm begging you to do more.
もっとしてくださいってお願いしてる
Look, look, look.
ほら、ほら、ほら、
Isn't your pussy completely white?
なんか まんこ真っ白じゃねえかよ
Yeah?
うん?
What do you want?
どうしてほしい?
Please try again.
も っと してください
Okay.
よ いしょ
Please do more.
もっとしてください
Where?
どこに?
Inside.
中に
Pussy.
まんこ
It's all words, isn't it?
単語じゃねえか、全部
Try to connect it and say it.
つなげて言ってみなさい
It's taught at university, right?
大学で教わってるでしょ
Please put the player inside your pussy.
まんこの中に選手出してください
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
Well done.
よくできました
Let me close my legs.
足閉じてもらおう
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
Now I can go in and say it.
入って言えるようになったね
Have you become a bit depressed?
だいぶ心落ちとけてきたかな?
I want you to feel good.
気持ちよくなってほしい
Wouldn't it make you feel a lot better and sell it?
いっぱい気持ちよくなって売れないかな?
Let's feel good together.
一緒に気持ちよくなろうよ
hey?
ね?
Here, close your legs properly.
ほら、ちゃんと足閉じて
Look here.
こっち見て
Show me your favorite girl.
すき目の子見せてほら
Where is it?
どこだよ
Look.
ほら
Go, look.
行け、ほら
Uncle, I'm not going yet.
まだおじさん、まだ行かないから
Uncle is going too.
お じさんも行っちゃうよ
Let's go together.
一緒に行こう
Look, look, it's going to fall apart.
ほら、ほら、ほっぱちぎれちゃうよ、
Look.
ほら
Let's go together.
一緒に行こうぜ
Here, let's get it out.
ほら、出すぞ
Please let me out, please.
出していって、お願いしなさい、ほら
I'll put it inside.
中に出すぞ
Let's go, let's go.
行 く ぞ、行くぞ
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
行 くぞ、行くぞ、行くぞ
Let's take care of it.
ちゃんとかかっておこう
both.
両方
Don't move.
動いちゃダメだよ
Just like that.
そのまま
Look, I got 5 pieces.
ほら、5個入っちゃったんだ
Put some effort into it.
力入れてほら
Look.
ほら
Wake up.
体を起こしてほら
Close your elbows.
ひじを縮めて
Ha, it's starting to droop.
はぁ、だれてきた
Hmm.
ふーんって
Ah, it's out, it's out.
あぁ、出た、出た
Did I put it out in the back?
奥のほうに出しちゃったかな?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Was it painful?
苦しかった?
You like pain, right?
苦しいの好きだろ?
I understand, uncle.
わかるんだ、おじさん
He looked really nice.
すごいいい顔してたよ
Much cuter than before I started.
始める前よりすごい可愛い
She was cute from the beginning, but she's even cuter now.
最初から可愛かったけど、今のほうが全然可愛いよ
It's cute even if I say so myself.
自分でもっていうところも可愛いよ
Thank you.
ありがとうね
Thank you for your help.
仲出しありがとうございました
That's nice.
いいですね
It suits you.
似合ってる
Have you ever been?
来たことある?
do not have.
ない
Please look at my pussy.
いったいおまんこ見てください
Please take a look at my pussy.
いっぱいおまんこ見てください
Shall I try blowing it in?
吹き入れてみようか
Yeah.
うん
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Yeah.
うん
Would you like me to make you feel better?
お じさんに気持ちよくしてもらおうか
I'll support you.
支えてあげるから
I guess I'll leave it there.
しておかな、ほら
Put your hands behind your head.
手、頭の後ろにして
Violently, you see.
激しく、ほら
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
Yes, yes.
はい、はい
Stand properly.
ちゃんと立って
Become a jerk.
ガニバタになって
Look, my eyes are dripping with juice.
すっげぇ目の汁垂らして、ほら
There's some salt dripping down below.
なんか塩汁垂れてるぞ、下に
Did you say something?
何か言ったの?
I don't know.
分かんない
Look, I've got something.
何か取れてるよ、ほら
Look!
見てごらん
I don't know.
分かんない
It's not like I don't understand.
分かんないじゃないし
It's dripping from your pussy.
あなたのおまんこから垂れてきたんだよ
where
どこ
With this, it will grow until
まで 生えるだろう、これなら
That's right.
そうだよ
Everyone's hands are on their toes now.
もう、 みんな手に力入ってるね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいか?
Try dehydrating yourself more intensely.
もっと激しく脱水してごらんよ
I can't tell, it feels good like that.
伝わらないよ、そんなんじゃ気持ちいいのが
Go, look.
いけ、ほら
Hey, more, more.
ほら、もっとだよ、もっと
I'll choke you, come on.
首締めてやるよ、ほら
You love neck tightening.
おまえ大好きな首締め
Here, go.
ほ ら、いけ
Did you go?
いったのか?
I put it out.
出してんだよ
Okay?
いいか?
Let go, here.
離すの、ほら
Okay, listen.
よし、いいか
Look, this change is good too.
ほら、こっちのチェンジもいいんだ
Hold my hand here, yeah.
手をこっちに握って、そうだ
Hold my hand here, yes.
手 をこっちに握って、そうだ
Come on, all the way.
ほら、奥まで
Deep, deep, deeper and deeper.
奥で、奥で、どんどん奥で
One more time.
もう一回だ
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
Look,
ほ ら、
Look.
ほ ら
Are you happy?
う れしいか?
幸せだろ?
There are also two changes.
チェンジ2本もあって
You threw up again.
また吐いちゃったね
You're trying to mess things up.
手荒らしようとしてるね
Just more, here.
もっとだけ、ほら
The box is already closed.
もう、箱閉まってる
Look.
ほら
Look carefully, here.
ちゃんと見ろ、ほら
You're trying to mess things up.
手荒らしようとしてるね
Just more, here.
もっとだけ、ほら
Look carefully, here.
ちゃんと見ろ、ほら
He told me to look at my lewd face.
ほら、スケベの私の顔を見てくださいって
Look carefully and see.
ちゃん と 見て、 ほら
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
ほ ら、 ほ ら
What are you doing?
何だしてんだよ
It feels so good.
なんか気持ちいいです
なんか気持ちいいよね
It feels so good.
I can't hear you.
聞こえない
You're probably moving your ass yourself, aren't you?
自分でケツ動かしてんじゃねえかよ、
Look.
ほら
You're lewd, aren't you?
スケベだな、お前
Does your dick feel good?
ちんこ、気持ちいいか?
It feels good already.
もう気持ちいいよ
That's enough, don't hold back.
もういいんだよ、我慢しないでいっちゃって
Look, look.
ほ ら、ほら
ほら、ほら
Lick it with all the drool on it.
よたれいっぱいつけて舐めて
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうだ
Wow, it feels so good.
うわ、すっごい気持ちいいよ
Oops.
おっと
Yeah, that's it.
そうそう、それだ
I'm going to screw it in at the bottom, my butt.
下先ねじ込ませるんだよ、お尻が
ah,
ああ、
That's it.
それ だ
Isn't your ass delicious?
おいしいか、おじさんのお尻
Add more drool.
もっとよたれいっぱいつけて
The old man's ass is healthy.
おじさんのケツはなおしいです
I'll put it in you, so let's make it even harder.
入れてあげるから、もっとガチガチにしてもらおう
What time do you go to Mango?
マンゴーどんな時間で行くの?
Please go.
行ってください
Oh, I went.
ああ、行った
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
Ah, that's cute.
ああ、かわいい
Go! Go! Go.
行け、行け、行け
Here, let's go.
ほら、行けよ
Can I get something out?
何 か出していいの?
Give me a lot.
いっぱい出して
Let's go, here.
行くぞ、ほら
Let's get it out, let's get it out.
出すぞ、出すぞ
Oh, oh, oh.
ああ、ああ、ああ
Okay, wait a minute.
よし、ちょっと待った
I'll go again.
また行くわ
Sorry.
ごめんな
It went inside.
奥に入っちゃったね
Let's put it away.
おくしにしよう
Drink?
飲んで?
picture?
え?
Don't drink.
飲むな
So, what should we do with this?
じゃあ、これでも何しようか
ah.
ああ
What should I do at home?
お家どうしよう
Home?
お家?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかったですか?
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました